The Boomerang is a drama film directed by Bertram Bracken.
Millionaire meat packer Peter Cameron, greedy for more money and power, maneuvers an alliance between his daughter Rose and
George Gray, the son of Cameron's business rival Max Gray, in order to increase his control of the food industry.
George, a lawyer, opposes the trust, and as a result is professionally ruined by
Cameron, disinherited by his father, and jilted by his fiancée.
Out on his own, George gets a job at a mill and starts at the bottom.
When an epidemic breaks out among his fellow laborers due to their eating spoiled meat from the trust, George secures
evidence of criminal practices which ultimately brings about the conviction of Cameron and the trust.
In championing the rights of the downtrodden, George
wins back Rose and reforms Cameron.
George Gray, played by Henry B. Walthall.
Peter Cameron, played by Melbourne MacDowell.
Rose Cameron, played by Nina Byron.
Nora Yorke, played by Helen Jerome Eddy.
Napoleon Snape, played by Jack McDonald.
Antonio Giannone, played by Nigel De Brulier.
The Boomerang is a 1919 American silent drama film directed by Bertram Bracken.
It stars Henry B.
Walthall, Melbourne MacDowell, and Nina Byron, and is based on the
novel of the same name by William Hamilton Osborne.
The tone is emotional.